{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810837639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810837639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810845517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810845516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810857749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810857748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810864162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810864162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810869588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810869588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810875033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810875033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810881755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810881755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810887312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810887312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810893117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810893117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810899094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810899094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810903941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810903941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810910270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810910270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810916017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810916016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810924223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810924223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 749e568d-2183-48d7-a2b7-bc7ec45acfd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810936092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810936092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810941847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810941847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810947079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810947078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810956431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810956431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810964597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810964596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810970471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810970471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810976304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810976304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810983583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810983583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810990054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810990054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549810995644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549810995643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811001408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811001407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811008466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811008466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 20eaf873-f8d1-43a2-95cb-60397c239e30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811022911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811022909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811023295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811023294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811023956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811023955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811024156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811024155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811025069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811025069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811027428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811027427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811027540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811027539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811033044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811033044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" b77a9fdd-9834-4cac-94ac-7a4aaf3312e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811044371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811044370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811052327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811052326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811053951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811053950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwito"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITO"," userResponse":" MWITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811057262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811057262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwito"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITO"," userResponse":" MWITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811058865","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811058865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sketi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SKETI"," userResponse":" SKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811063525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811063525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sketi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811065096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811065095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811069176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811069175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811070760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811070760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811074610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811074610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811076160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811076160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811079631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811079631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811081193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811081193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811084938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811084938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811086494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811086494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811089919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811089918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811091481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811091480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811095202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811095201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811096767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811096767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811100589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811100589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811102597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811102597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811102764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811102764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811108256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811108256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 4cc9986b-bdf1-4f68-9a82-ebd439961fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811120500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811120499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811120740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811120740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811121190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811121190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811121401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811121400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811122156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811122156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811126037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811126037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811128411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811128411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811132608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811132608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811137477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811137477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811138229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811138229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811138964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811138963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811141304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811141304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811142167","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811142167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811142690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811142690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811143433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811143433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811143781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811143781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811145476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811145476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811146014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811146014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" START_ANARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811147039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811147039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811148756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811148756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811148926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811148926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811149922","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811149922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811151025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811151024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811154023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811154023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811156383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811156383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811157567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811157566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811158038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811158038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811158280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811158279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811159033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811159032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811159457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811159456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811161172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811161172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811162276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811162276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811162978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811162977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811163143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811163143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811163859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811163859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811164359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811164359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811166675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811166674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811167309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811167308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811168132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811168131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811168968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811168968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811170443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811170443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811171034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811171034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811171544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811171543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811172855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811172855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811175270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811175270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811176295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811176294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811176902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811176902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811177459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811177459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811179706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811179705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811180309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811180307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" START_ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811181346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811181345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811183102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811183102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811185795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811185795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811187527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811187527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811189856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811189856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811190720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811190720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811191328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811191328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811192171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811192171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811194572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811194572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" START_MUMBI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811196096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811196096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811197525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811197525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811198404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811198404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811199502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811199501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811200087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811200086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811200827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811200827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811203120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811203119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811204265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811204265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811205360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811205359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811208150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811208150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811208160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811208160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811209079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811209078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811211726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811211725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811212576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811212575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811213507","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811213506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811214373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811214373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811216094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811216094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811217368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811217368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811218200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811218200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" START_ANAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811219924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811219923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" START_ANAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811221784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811221784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811223081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811223081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811228312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811228312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811230903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811230902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811231215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811231215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811231776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811231775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811233786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811233786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811233940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811233940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811235582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811235582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811237270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811237269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811238285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811238284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811239876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811239876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811249017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811249016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811251336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811251335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811252990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811252990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811253614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811253614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811255349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811255349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811256340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811256339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811258107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811258107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811260264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811260263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811262134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811262134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811264450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811264450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811265729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811265729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811267993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811267992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811268102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811268102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811271109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811271109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811273214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811273213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811275231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811275231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811275493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811275492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 8ad33202-88c7-41ab-93be-2e952776dbd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811288755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811288755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811288988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811288988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811289432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811289431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811289638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811289638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811289654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811289654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811289753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811289753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811296957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811296957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811302738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811302737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811309159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811309159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 717fe286-b771-44de-a54f-cf5067dddc0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811323019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811323019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811327948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811327948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811333154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811333154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" treni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811338962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811338962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" mende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811345484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811345484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811350491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811350491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811357511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811357511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyigu_nyigu-ukiwa-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyigu"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811362879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811362879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" sauti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811368159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811368159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" mpira"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811375096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811375096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ofisi_vumbi-ofisi-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ofisi"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811381911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811381911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811387637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811387636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811392355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811392354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 9115fc2e-8035-4d30-a4b8-0b957d6ad05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811403303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811403303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811409147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811409147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811416707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811416707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811423992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811423992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811431920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811431920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811449841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811449841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811457409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811457408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811471492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811471492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811478040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811478040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811488653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811488653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811500926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811500925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811511591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811511591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811522426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811522425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811528190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811528189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" d5dde544-6f99-4c10-9ab2-57db56036144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811537509","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811537509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 436a8945-c309-4329-b460-f7ff0ca0b550"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811537732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811537732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 436a8945-c309-4329-b460-f7ff0ca0b550"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811537900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811537899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 436a8945-c309-4329-b460-f7ff0ca0b550"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811537974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811537974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 436a8945-c309-4329-b460-f7ff0ca0b550"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811558100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811558100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811565840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811565840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811570072","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811570071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811575060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811575060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811581870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811581870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811586850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811586848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811601227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811601227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 7526e0c8-f44e-4f9e-b696-f3b1db7ce6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811613817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811613817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811618686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811618686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811624413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811624413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811630946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811630946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811637196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811637196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811643035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811643035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811648280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811648280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811653988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811653988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811658627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811658627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811664638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811664637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811692066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811692066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811698730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811698729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" e9f70fc7-393f-4e33-9573-16795bd5c8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811712617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811712617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811723695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811723695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811730432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811730432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811738429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811738429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811746857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811746857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811753939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811753939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811760874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811760874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811768846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811768846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811776449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811776449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811782983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811782982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811788720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811788719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811796849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811796848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 6b94dd58-e6a9-49b1-97dc-aac276f0a482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811814402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811814401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811814674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811814674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811815478","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811815478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811815582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811815582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811816425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811816425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811816868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811816867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811817894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811817894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811819037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811819037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811819391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811819391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811819987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811819987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811820870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811820870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811827536","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811827536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811832245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811832245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811832367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811832367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811838399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811838399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 32e953d8-50ad-4793-853d-ccbdae0d81ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811860772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811860771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nzito_wapya_mmeze"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811867405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811867403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kanga_langu_randa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811874106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811874106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ajuza_ngozi_aling"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811880783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811880781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kimya_mkoba_akpaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811887426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811887426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mvivu_mioto_rahim"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811894087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811894085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ncede_mwili_amung"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811901608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811901608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ncede_mwili_amung"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811908253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811908253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amani_usemi_mkosa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811914916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811914916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_laini_milio_miale"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811922447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811922447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_laini_milio_miale"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811929081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811929080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nione_meupe_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811935775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811935774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bonde_kweli_mbizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811943283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811943283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bonde_kweli_mbizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811956463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811956462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 03e9d4e9-3e01-41b5-a210-7364dc2bc5ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.5.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_bonde_kweli_mbizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811965432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811965432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811965481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811965481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811972994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811972993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811977985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811977985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811982772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811982772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811992608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811992608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549811998981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549811998981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812004436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812004436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812009479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812009479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812018371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812018370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812023166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812023166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812030150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812030149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812034732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812034732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812046502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812046502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812052370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812052370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812059562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812059562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812068568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812068567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812073681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812073680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812079031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812079031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812089043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812089041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812102766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812102765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.5.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812108180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812108180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812112644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812112644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" a5b2057b-1710-47a1-bc16-54878e0acd2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812128120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812128120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812128643","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812128643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812128898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812128898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812129522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812129522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812132306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812132306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812133703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812133703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812135197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812135197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812137366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812137366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812138761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812138760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" START_LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812140237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812140237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812144968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812144968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549812145113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549812145113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_180004"," gameId":" 065653b4-df46-4b05-8df4-ae4dd5b9622b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}